(Leonard:)Good luck catching a man
with that attitude.
(Sheldon:)Boy, oh, boy, this vacation
is off to a wonderful start.
(Sheldon:)The smell of formaldehyde.
(Sheldon:)The whir of the centrifuge.
(Sheldon:)The distant chatter of lab animals
being dispatched for dissection.
(Sheldon:)Mm, I can already feel my cares
just meIting away.
(Amy:)I'm excited to work with my boyfriend.
It's romantic.
(Sheldon:)Way to kill the mood.
(Amy:)Come on, Sheldon. We can be like
Marie Curie and her husband, Pierre...
(Amy:)...who spent their days
working side by side...
(Amy:)...bathed in the glow of their love
and the radium that uItimately killed her.
(Amy:)Screw Beauty and the Beast,
that's the love story Disney should tell.
(Sheldon:)Okay. What do we start with?
Maybe, uh, splicing some genes.
Clone a sheep.
Perhaps, uh, grow a human ear
on a mouse's back?
"Ha, ha! I'm a freak."